{"test_questions": [[{"question": "What type of failure occurs when Oracle fails due to an operating system or computer hardware failure?", "opta": "Application failure", "optb": "Instance Failure", "optc": "Media Failure", "optd": "Rollback failure", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which statement about sequences is not true?", "opta": "A sequence is an object that generates a sequential series of unique numbers.", "optb": "Sequences are most often used to provide values for surrogate keys.", "optc": "NextVal and CurrVal are both sequence methods.", "optd": "Sequences guarantee valid surrogate key values.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which prefixes are available to Oracle triggers?", "opta": ":new only", "optb": ":old only", "optc": "Both :new and :old", "optd": "Neither :new nor :old", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In creating a procedure, you may get a message if you have compile errors. Which of the following is true?", "opta": "The line numbers reported match the line numbers you see in your text editor.", "optb": "SQL*Plus will automatically show the errors to you.", "optc": "To see the errors, enter SHOW ERRORS in SQL*Plus.", "optd": "If there are no syntax errors, you will receive the message \"NO ERRORS.\"", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not true about indexes?", "opta": "Indexes are created to enforce uniqueness on columns.", "optb": "Indexes are created to enable fast retrieval by column values.", "optc": "Columns that are frequently used with equal conditions in WHERE clauses are good candidates for indexes.", "optd": "Indexes are created with the ALTER TABLE command.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not true of SQL views?", "opta": "Oracle views cannot use the ORDER BY clause in view definitions.", "optb": "Oracle views are created using the standard SQL-92 CREATE VIEW command.", "optc": "Oracle views can by queried.", "optd": "The SQL-92 standard does not allow the use of the ORDER BY clause in view definitions.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL*Plus will finish the statement and execute it when the user types in this:", "opta": "A left slash ( \\ ) followed by [Enter].", "optb": "A colon ( : ) followed by [Enter].", "optc": "A semicolon ( ; ) followed by [Enter].", "optd": "A period ( . ) followed by [Enter].", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is NOT an Oracle-supported trigger?", "opta": "BEFORE", "optb": "DURING", "optc": "AFTER", "optd": "INSTEAD OF", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "After a table has been created, its structure can be modified using the SQL command:", "opta": "UPDATE TABLE [TableName].", "optb": "MODIFY TABLE [TableName].", "optc": "ALTER TABLE [TableName].", "optd": "CHANGE TABLE [TableName].", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not true about modifying table columns?", "opta": "You can drop a column at any time.", "optb": "You can add a column at any time as long as it is a NULL column.", "optc": "You can increase the number of characters in character columns or the number of digits in numeric columns", "optd": "You cannot increase or decrease the number of decimal places.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Of the three ways to create an Oracle database, which one is the easiest and most recommended?", "opta": "Using the Oracle Database Configuration Assistant.", "optb": "Using the Oracle-supplied database creation procedures.", "optc": "Using the SQL CREATE DATABASE command.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What Oracle backup and recover file contains user and system data?", "opta": "Control file", "optb": "Datafile", "optc": "OnLine ReDo file", "optd": "Offline ReDo file", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using SQL*Plus, Oracle commands, column names, table names and all other database elements:", "opta": "are case insensitive.", "optb": "are case sensitive.", "optc": "must always be in lower case.", "optd": "must always be in upper case.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which SQL phrase is not supported by Oracle?", "opta": "ON DELETE CASCADE", "optb": "ON UPDATE CASCADE", "optc": "CREATE SEQUENCE [SequenceName]", "optd": "DROP SEQUENCE [SequenceName]", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the type of Oracle backup in which all uncommitted changes have been removed from the datafiles?", "opta": "Full backup", "optb": "Consistent backup", "optc": "Inconsistent backup", "optd": "Differential backup", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "You have linked SQL*Plus to an external text editor. To invoke the text editor for use within SQL*Plus, which command do you use?", "opta": "Open [FileName]", "optb": "Show [FileName]", "optc": "Alter [FileName]", "optd": "Edit [FileName]", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The default extension for an Oracle SQL*Plus file is:", "opta": ".txt.", "optb": ".pls.", "optc": ".ora.", "optd": ".sql.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An Oracle System Change Number (SCN):", "opta": "is a value that is incremented whenever a dirty read occurs.", "optb": "is incremented whenever a deadlock occurs.", "optc": "is a value that keeps track of explicit locks.", "optd": "is a value that is incremented whenever database changes are made.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To obtain the structure of an Oracle table, the command to use is:", "opta": "STRUCTURE [TableName].", "optb": "DESCRIBE [TableName].", "optc": "DESCRIBE STRUCTURE [TableName].", "optd": "DESC TABLE [TableName].", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To see the contents of the SQL*Plus buffer, type:", "opta": "CONTENTS.", "optb": "BUFFER.", "optc": "CURRENT.", "optd": "LIST.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}